[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This character, who chased villains in Live and Let Die, is the short-tempered U.S. sheriff in The Man with the Golden Gun?", "correct_answer": "J.W. Pepper", "incorrect_answers": ["J.W. Salt", "J.W. Vinegar", "J.W. Mustard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Large penguins can dive nearly 2,000 feet.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish this old phrase:\n\nWhen you call a dog, he comes right over to you. When you call a cat, she________________.", "correct_answer": "takes a message", "incorrect_answers": ["climbs the curtains", "runs away from you", "thinks its dinner time"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wind is one of the five elements.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Navins last name in the 1979 comedy The Jerk?", "correct_answer": "Johnson", "incorrect_answers": ["Singer", "Kameston", "Maltin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Diamond is the birthstone of people who were born in this month.", "correct_answer": "April", "incorrect_answers": ["March", "June", "February"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a separate AFI poll that ranks 100 of  Americas Most Inspiring Movies, the 1946 movie Its a Wonderful Life leads the pack.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following behaviors is not typical for the Chinese Crested dog?", "correct_answer": "Pant to keep cool", "incorrect_answers": ["Bark", "Lift a leg to urinate", "Wag their tail when happy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote The Murders in the Rue Morgue, the book considered the first detective story?", "correct_answer": "Edgar Allan Poe", "incorrect_answers": ["Charles Lennox", "Jules Verne", "Sir Arthur Conan Doyle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This board game, first published by the Milton Bradley Company in 1931, derived from a guessing paper and pencil game, and has also a one-person puzzle version.", "correct_answer": "Battleship", "incorrect_answers": ["Liu po", "Titan", "Stratego"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are hard drives and floppy disks read?", "correct_answer": "Magnetically", "incorrect_answers": ["Laser", "Beam of Nuclear Radiation", "Sensor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the beginning of the movie The Graduate, Benjamin returns home from this Northeast university.", "correct_answer": "It was never mentioned in the movie.", "incorrect_answers": ["Rutgers", "Harvard", "Yale"]}]